Hello!
"English Grammar Workout: 700+ Tough Drills"
You find what you were looking for?
No. Maybe I should just order it in...
You could ask a clerk to help.
Nah, I'll just keep looking for it!
Mmkay, I'm gonna grab this.
Oh, I'll come with you.
I'm gonna buy something, too.
Ow!
They've got some game magazines
over there! Lemme show you, c'mon!
Sure.
"Horimiya"
Toru!
What? You taking out the trash?
Yup. You grab the burnables.
So I'm helping you now? Whoa!
This one's heavy as shit! I see what
you're doing, Yoshikawa. Real smooth.
Huh? What could you possibly be talking about?
"You're Here, I'm Here"
Oh, right! That DVD I wanted is out today.
Come with me to pick it up later.
Urgh...
I'll let you borrow it later!
The actor playing the shopkeeper is so hot!
--And not just that...
--Ever since Hori and Miyamura started dating,
--Yoshikawa's been giving me lots of attention.
--And not just that...
--Are you even listening to me right now?
--I am, thank you!
Ugh, you're so annoy--
Kono-san!
You okay?! I'm so sorry!
No, I was the one who ran into you.
How embarrassing.
Hold on a sec!
I'll be right back!
Oh, okay.
Sorry! We gotta watch where we're going.
No, you're fine.
I really hope it doesn't leave a stain.
Hey, Yoshikawa-san...
A-Are you dating Ishikawa-kun?
No, we're not dating.
Oh.
I wasn't sure if you'd be able
to wear that home, Kono-san.
And I figured Yoshikawa's
is probably too small...
"Ishikawa"
And I figured Yoshikawa's
is probably too small...
"Ishikawa"
Mine's gonna be big, but at least
it's something. Sorry again!
Huh?! You want me to wear this?
Oh, crap, I should've just brought you yours!
No! I'll borrow yours! Thank you!
"Student Council Room"
What's with the jacket?
It's a long story.
Where's Remi?
Oh, she had to head home
to take care of some stuff.
She did open the window, though.
She's keeping on top of her window duty, huh.
Hey, Sengoku-kun.
What is it that you like about her?
I can't believe you're asking me that, too.
I-Is it that shocking for me to ask?!
Sorry, sorry.
I guess the fact that she's not
very strong, so she needs me around.
So you want someone weak to stand
next to you to make you look strong?
No, that's not it! I don't control her,
just, like, I want to protect her!
She makes me want to protect her.
But that's kind of what I like about her.
I'm not even that strong in the first place.
But Remi makes me want to
be stronger, if just for her sake.
Because she's behind me, pushing me forward,
I have the strength to give
her the push she needs, too.
In the end, she's protecting me.
Just like how she protects you, right, Sakura?
You look really cute, Sakura!
Yeah, she does.
She gives me courage.
Courage to try just a little bit harder.
Ishikawa-kun?
Oh, hey, Kono-san.
Thank you for lending me this.
Sorry it took me so long to give
it back. I wanted to wash it first.
Aww, you didn't have to
go through all that trouble!
--It's okay. Thank you again for the help.
--Ishikawa! Can I borrow you, dude?
Coming!
Later.
Hey, uh...
I-I made too many cookies, so, uh...
Huh? Are those for me? Sweet, thanks!
I-I hope you like them!
Yo, these are great! I'm impressed!
Especially these sakura-pink ones!
D-Do you like Sakura?
Sakura? Yeah, I love sakura.
Ishikawa!
I said I'm coming!
Sorry!
Oh, but if you make these again,
bring more! I love 'em!
Took you long enough!
Gimme a break!
Nice! I got the last one--
Why'd you do that, Yuki?
You've been looking for that forever.
She looked like she wanted it,
and I can always find it another day.
It's no biggie.
Ishikawa, someone's lookin' for ya!
Coming!
Hey, Yuki.
I haven't seen you and Toru
together for a bit. Everything okay?
Yeah. He's probably off
somewhere eating cookies.
What's that supposed to mean?
"Peach Tea"
I've only known her for three years,
but I can read her pretty well.
Ooh, we've got study hall next! Sweet!
The less she wants you to know
she's upset, the bigger she smiles.
Even when she desperately wants something,
she'll never say so out loud.
And she'll never say "I love this"
or "I want this" with all her heart.
So the things she loves or
wants tend to escape her.
I wanted to thank you for
lending me that handkerchief.
I'm good, thanks.
Oh! Wow, I love cookies!
Thanks, Kono-san!
For real, though, thanks, Kono-san.
I'm glad you like them!
I do! They're so frickin' good!
I wanted to thank you.
They're good.
Might as well just take them
if they're gonna be this good.
I'm so ugly.
Huh? A cake?
Yeah. I've never made one before.
It doesn't have to be fancy.
I just want it to taste good.
Guess that's kind of hard, though.
You know, Yoshikawa-san,
I wasn't born knowing how to bake a cake.
Huh?
Nobody's good at anything when they first start.
If you mess up, just give it another shot.
Right!
Wow.
These took you a whole week?
They're cupcakes, right?
We're really starting from
square one, here, huh?!
Why don't you want Toru in on this?
B-Because he'd totally make fun of me!
He wouldn't, especially if he
knew you're making them for him.
I'm not making them for him!
Hey, there you are!
You having a party? Why wasn't I invited?
Don't look!
Is this a cupcake?
Give it back!
Ugh, these taste like crap.
Hey!
Like, absolute crap.
I know, okay?
Can't wait for the next batch!
Same!
Same here.
I'm on it!
Miyamura went up to Hokkaido, right?
Yeah, he's visiting family
up there for five days.
So he won't be here all week.
Wait, then I'll have to
read different lines in class!
Miyamura was gonna read the fifth line, so...
Ugh, now mine's super long!
Oh, this one's way easier.
Made it to Hokkaido. It's a lot cooler up here.
My battery's almost dead.
And I forgot my charger...
Uncle, can I borrow your phone charger?
Sure, does mine work with yours?
Oh.
Nope...
Can we go to the convenience store?
We're a little busy, honey.
I can't drive you anywhere right now.
Hold tight for a bit, okay?
You're gonna drink two?
Yeah, uh, I'm thirsty.
Gotta stay hydrated in this heat.
You keep downing those sugary drinks
and you'll get fat, Yoshikawa.
Three more days.
"Made it to Hokkaido
It's a lot cooler up here"
Bye-bye, Hori-san!
See you tomorrow!
Are you waiting for someone?
No.
Oh.
Bye!
Kyoko, that isn't my bowl.
Oh, that's my bro's bowl!
Are you trying to push my buttons or something?
No! I just forgot.
Really? Guess even you slip up now and then.
"Yogurt Farm"
Miyamura comes back today, yeah?
Sometime this evening, right?
Or later than that?
No idea.
Hey, I wanna watch Hurricane Star!
It's already started!
Why're you binging the news?
Our next story tonight: carry-on
restrictions at airports continue to...
Wait, what?
Hey, Kyoko!
And it's back.
Shindo, Shindo...
Ishikawa-kun says the test
got postponed. Aww, man...
"Hori-san"
Izumi?
I'm so--
You big dummy.
I never knew how long five days could feel.
Welcome back.
Hey, uh... thanks.
But now I do.
"Hurry up and get back here, dummy."
"Student Council Room"
What doesn't he like?
Miyamura doesn't like horror movies.
But he'll still watch them with me,
so maybe he does like 'em after all.
Because you're making him watch them.
Hey, Hori,
you're gonna push him away if you
keep watching all that scary stuff.
You think so?
A cute girl gleefully watching
slasher flicks is pretty creepy...
C'mon now, I'm not that cute.
That wasn't the point there, Hori.
I agree with Yoshikawa! It's a total turnoff.
Y-You think so?
I borrowed this for us, Hori-san.
It has lots of dogs in it!
Can we watch Right Behind You:
The Third Nightmare instead?
Sure.
You're gonna push him away if you
keep watching all that scary stuff.
Miyamura, so, uh, this movie's, uh...
...gonna be pretty scary, huh?
What're you talking about?
Compared to the PG-13 gorefests we always watch,
this G-rated one's totally harmless!
Yuki!
You should pretend to be scared!
I'm scared!
You scared me...
Ayasaki-san!
Maybe this just won't work...
Maybe you could hold his hand?
Wow, I'm so scared...
I just want to have fun
watching a movie with him...
I'm sorry I'm such a scaredy-cat. I'm so sorry.
N-No, don't apologize!
It's not your fault, Miyamura.
I know. Give me a second, I need a moment alone.
He's totally done with me...
It's over!
I'm so lame.
Hori-san?
I'm not cute at all.
Huh? What do you mean? You're really cute.
I don't get scared. I can't even act scared.
I can't do anything cute. I'm hopeless.
Wait, were you doing all that for me?
Who cares, you big dummy?!
I'm sorry, Hori-san. I was too
freaked-out and scared to notice.
Why do you keep apologizing to me?!
Don't look at me, dummy!
You're the big dummy here, Hori-san.
I didn't fall in love with
a "normal girl." I fell for you.
Let's go watch the rest of the movie.
It's raining pretty hard.
Yeah, wow.
I did, too.
I fell for him.
His long eyelashes, his scaredy-cat jumps,
his sarcastic quips,
how thin he feels in my arms.
His voice, and... and...
Izumi.
What's up?
I'm listening to your heart.
What's it saying?
How cold it is.
Your hands and ears are really cold, Miyamura.
Probably from the rain.
Could be.
You can't go home in this downpour.
There was a heat within me,
and I wanted Miyamura to feel it, too.
Look, it's you, me, and my big sis!
Sota?
You know, she's... my big sister.
Are you worried I'll take her away from you?
I won't. She's your big sister, Sota.
And you're my bro?
Yeah. I'm your big bro.
I won't take your big sister away, Sota.
But could I have Kyoko?
Okay.
"Next Time: The Truth Deception Reveals"
Ow, ow...
Your hair's getting longer.
If you cut it again, everyone'll see that mark.
Why'd she bite you?
I have no idea.
Looks like a mark of ownership,
but maybe I shouldn't tell him that.